HI removed, cleaned
and corrected by Lunar Team
- Hey, Tommy.
- Morning, Mr. Jane. You're all set.
- Have a good one.
- You too. Have a good one.
Hi, Tommy.
- Thanks a lot.
- Have a good day.
- Good morning, everybody.
- What's so good about it?
Here, have a file.
The division is being audited again.
No problem.
Let me just put milk in this and I'll dig in.
"No problem"? What's with her?
You mean why isn't she cynical
and jaded like you?
Notice her relaxed body language?
The general sense of emotional satisfaction.
Yeah.
Someone's engaged
her romantic interest.
- Who?
- Well, I couldn't say.
No, she's focused on her work.
That's all.
Then I have to assume the man
that kissed her outside...
- ...was making an embarrassing mistake.
- What?
- Who kissed her?
- Uh, didn't catch his name.
That knucklehead from Payroll.
Been stalking her like a chicken.
- What did this man look like?
- Lisbon.
- How do you stalk a chicken?
- You know what I'm talking about.
"There's a very large bomb nearby.
Are you smart enough to find it?"
- Another bomb threat. Third this year.
- Not on my phone, it isn't.
They don't usually come through CBI,
but that's what drills are for.
The text read,
"Are you smart enough to find it?"
- I think this was directed at me.
- Of course you think this is about you.
Just relax. It could be a hoax.
It could be.
- Where is the bomb squad?
- On their way.
PD did an initial sweep.
They haven't found anything.
"Are you smart enough to find it?"
Okay, listen, if this really is about Jane,
I don't want him just...
- Hey.
- Jane.
Jane, stop right there.
Minelli. Yes, sir.
- Jane.
- Let me explain what happened.
Jane got a text on his phone.
The text said a very large bomb.
A large bomb can only be transported
in a large car.
They didn't say inside CBI,
they said nearby.
- Ergo the parking lot. It's simple.
- Exactly.
They challenged you to an easy puzzle.
They want you to find the bomb.
If there is a bomb.
Probably just a hoax like you said.
Yes, sir. I'll have him back in a minute.
I'm trying, sir. Yes, I assure you
he understands the situation.
Hey, Lisbon! Found it!
Oh, no.
- Shoot it out. Shoot it with your gun.
- I can't. There's no time. Come on.
Jane, come on, let's go.
Come on, run, Jane.
Jane, run. I mean it.
Come on. Jane. Come on.
Run. Come on.
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
- You all right?
- Okay.
- I'm fine.
I'm gonna get...
I need an ambulance now.
No. No ambulance.
I just got something in my eyes.
I can't see. I can't see.
You're a lucky man, Mr. Jane.
This could've been much worse.
Yes, that's what people keep telling me.
But why is it I can't see, doctor?
Well, there's a moderate concussion
with some short-term memory loss.
Disorientation, headache,
and, of course, fleeting blindness.
Most likely due to floating blood clots
in the vessels around the eyes...
...demonstrating a CVI,
or cortical visual impairment.
How long will his vision be affected?
It's hard to say, really. The body's
healing powers are unpredictable.
But 48 to 72 hours is the norm.
We must wait and see, so to speak.
Humor. Great.
Everybody loves a witty doctor
in times of trouble.
I've heard enough.
Think you can take this outside?
Mr. Jane, this is temporary.
Your sight will return
and you'll be back to work.
- But it takes time and patience.
- Time I have.
But patience I lost a while ago.
You're alive. Appreciate it.
Oh, I do. Believe me, I do.
If you'll excuse me,
I'll check in again later.
Thank you, doctor.
Ow!
I'll do worse
if you don't stop mouthing off...
- ...to people trying to help.
- Pinched me.
- How is he?
- Guess what, he's a bad patient.
- Who'd have thought?
- I'm not a bad patient. She's a bad visitor.
What'd you find out?
The victim is James Medina, 44.
A stockbroker out of Highlands.
Van wasn't his. It was stolen yesterday.
We're digging up everything on Medina.
Is it possible he was on
some bizarre suicide mission?
No.
I looked in his eyes.
That was very much a man
who didn't wanna be where he was.
Whoever did this wanted me
to watch James Medina die in terror.
They nearly killed you too.
- That wasn't the intention.
- What then?
"You're next" was written
on the man's forehead.
Why?
I don't know why.
- You're gonna be fine.
- Yeah, probably.
- We're gonna find who did this.
- Good.
- Don't look at each other like that.
- Like what? You can't see.
I can feel. I can feel your pity.
Please, would you stop? We'll be back.
Later, man.
- Thank you, Rosie.
- Sure.
Alrighty, you two. I love you.
You be good with your
Auntie Rose now, okay?
Promise?
Mm-hm.
- See you.
- Bye, Mom.
Bye.
- Sweet kids.
- Thank you.
- Jim loved them very much.
- I'm sorry, Mrs. Medina.
But we have to ask you a couple
questions about your husband.
He didn't seem preoccupied?
Troubled by anything unusual?
Preoccupied, yes.
But there's nothing unusual about that.
My husband was a stockbroker.
Nowadays that's like being
a professional gambler.
What about your personal finances?
I never let Jim put all
our money into the market.
Did he mention any particular client
being unhappy?
Do you know how many clients
lost money in the last six months?
A lot of people are angry
and blame their brokers.
Jim's received hate mail,
phone calls, e-mail.
Any specific threats? He mention names?
There was an ex-coworker,
Terry Andrews.
He came by the house a few times.
He was very threatening.
Thank you.
Terence Carter Andrews, 46 years old.
Worked for two years at Lynch-Halstead
in the junior trader program.
Tax records indicate
he worked as a guard...
...for security companies
that cover the state capitol.
He was a statehouse employee?
He worked here?
That's what it says.
He also has a rap sheet on him.
- Domestic violence and two DUIs.
- This is it?
Where is he working now?
Guest-relations manager
at something called Hype.
You, Little Miss Fierce, can come in.
Lose the backup dancer.
He's too, too butch.
Get lost, Fluffy.
- Are you Terence Andrews?
- What do you guys want?
Do people call you Terry or Terence?
They call me Mr. Andrews.
Someone killed James Medina today.
Thoughts?
Yeah. I'd like to buy whoever did it
a nice bottle of French brandy.
- You flat-out hated him, huh?
- Yeah. Yeah, I did.
- You think I had something to do with it?
- Yeah.
Why don't you come downtown with us,
answer questions?
No, I don't think so.
You know why? Because I didn't do it.
- Come on, let's go.
- Get off.
- And you want some too?
- No, thank you.
Everybody step back,
give him air. Fun's over.
Are you okay, Mr. Andrews?
Hey, aren't you supposed to be
in the hospital?
- No.
- Yes, you are.
They had enough of me.
Can't say I blame them.
Officer Powell here was kind enough
to give me a ride back.
Thank you, I guess.
- Have a good one, Mr. Jane.
- Yeah.
Go ahead, talk to your boyfriend.
I don't mind.
Shush.
- Why are you embarrassed?
- I'm not.
- What the hell?
- Doctor's orders.
She said the best thing
was to get back to work.
She did not. She said you insulted the ward
and were a pain in the ass.
No. So?
So you can't do that.
Well, what was I supposed to do?
Just sit there and listen to television?
Besides, the food was terrible.
- You need rest.
- I need to work.
- You're blind.
- No problem.
My other senses are heightened.
Super-heightened. I'm like Daredevil.
- Now if you'll excuse me.
- Okay.
Okay.
Heightened.
Where were you yesterday morning?
My shift at the club ended at 3:30.
I went back to my place,
watched a little bit of TV...
...and then I went to bed.
I slept till about 11:00 or so.
- Can anyone vouch for that time frame?
- Nope. I live alone.
On account of my lady walked out
when I lost my job.
- Sorry. Don't mind me.
- Jane?
What is this? What is this?
- He's blind.
- Yeah.
Sorry.
Cool, huh?
Yeah. So did you kill James Medina?
Did I kill James Medina? Screw him.
I didn't kill him.
I could have and I wanted to.
But I didn't.
What are you doing?
Have we ever met before?
- No.
- So, what happened?
Why did you fight in the first place?
I was a junior trader in the company.
He had been picking on me.
I took a job his nephew wanted.
Anyway, a freaking envelope
falls off his desk.
"Pick it up," he said. Like that.
"Pick it up."
"I don't think so.
Pick it up your own damn self," I said.
Big deal.
But I guess he figures, "I'm just...
You know, I'm gonna snap my fingers
and totally just ruin this dude's life."
Can I hold your hand?
Artistic fingers.
- Soft.
- Don't do that.
Nice to talk with you, Terry. Be well.
- You can let him go.
- That's not your call.
Well, I didn't say you must let him go.
I said that you can, if you want.
- Being that he's innocent.
- Thank you.
- Jane?
- Oh, that was loud. That scared me.
How many times do I have to tell you
to stop interrupting interviews like that?
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Just a minute.
- What are you doing?
How will I know if I can see or not
if I have bandages on?
Ow.
Here goes.
Well?
- Black as night.
- I'm sorry.
- Never mind. Andrews didn't do it.
- You sense that with your super powers?
Yes, I did. He's filled with anger.
But not fearful, guilty, murderous anger.
That has a tang of ammonia about it.
His is a more clean, righteous anger.
Lemony.
- Lemony?
- This blind thing really works.
Without vision, I can tune into
my other senses much more clearly.
That's great. Let me go make you
a superhero costume.
What do you want to be called?
What are you doing?
I wanna know what your face feels like
when you're smiling.
So, what's the deal, boss?
Have Forensics check him
for any explosives residue.
- If he comes up clean, let him go.
- Will do.
I'm convinced there's a connection
between Medina and me.
Before you make me that
superhero costume...
- ...could you take me to visit his widow?
- Maybe.
Thank you. And incidentally,
you're smelling particularly good today.
Is that cinnamon in the mix
there somewhere? Lisbon?
Your tea is right in front of you,
Mr. Jane.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Mrs. Medina, we don't mean
to keep you from your family.
We just have
a few more questions to ask you.
I understand. I'm happy to help.
I can feel what a warm,
caring home this is.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
I think whoever did this was targeting
your husband and me also.
I don't know why,
but something links us.
- I have to ask, have we ever met before?
- Not that I know of.
Would it be a terrible inconvenience...
...to show me some
of your husband's personal things?
- Jewelry, anything he used a lot.
- Sure, I guess. Why?
Holding something of James'
would help me pick up a feel for him.
- Get a sense of his being.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Thank you.
"Sense of his being"?
What are you playing at?
Just go with it.
I have to practice this touchy-feely stuff.
It's been a while.
- You're not gonna be blind forever.
- No, right.
Because bad stuff like this doesn't happen
nearly as often as people think.
Bifocals?
Jim couldn't read without them.
He was considering surgery, but I liked
the way he looked in his glasses.
He held off because of me.
- Did he like horses?
- We liked to ride together.
We were planning to take a trip
up to the coast this fall.
- This feels expensive.
- Yes.
He only wore that to business functions.
There's a jewel with an engraving
on the back. What is that engraving?
It's a bull. It was a company gift
from Lynch-Halstead.
A little too much bling
for Jim's everyday taste.
Jane?
Well, thank you for your time,
Mrs. Medina.
The watch I recalled was the exact same.
It had the same engraving on the back
as James Medina's.
And his was from Lynch-Halstead.
Thank you.
So years ago, I must have done a reading
for someone connected to the firm.
- You don't know who?
- I can't remember.
I'm trying to see the woman's face
and recall her name. I can't do it.
But she paid you and was hurt so badly...
- ...she's still holding a grudge.
- Probably.
- The man's blind. Go easy maybe.
- Sorry.
No, it's okay. You're fine.
Did you keep a record of
all your customers or clients...
- ...whatever you called them?
- Yeah, had to.
I had to keep track of the lies
I'd already told.
- Where are they?
- Probably on a disk in my boxes.
Over there, I expect.
Van Pelt, why don't you help Jane
find his records?
First, could someone please
make me a cup of tea?
Is that a yes?
Rigsby.
Thank you.
- Did you put the milk...?
- Milk in first. Yeah, like you asked.
- You're sure the water boiled...?
- It was truly boiling. Yep.
- Tastes weird.
- Tastes weird?
Jane, I need to ask you a favor.
I need you to find out from Van Pelt
about this guy she's dating.
- You know, what's the score?
- The score?
- Is it serious? Are they...? You know.
- Ask her yourself.
Right. You know the situation.
It's against the rules.
Relationships between coworkers.
- What are you, a man or a mouse?
- A man, obviously.
- Could have fooled me.
- If it's that guy from Payroll, I'll kill him.
That would be
a strong romantic statement.
Women like a man that'd kill for them.
- Hey, Van Pelt?
- Don't.
- What? Trust me.
- Oh, no.
- Honesty is better.
- No.
What's up?
Grace, a personal question.
Rigsby and I were wondering...
...who is this man you were
kissing by the coffee cart?
- That's none of your business.
- Not from Payroll?
Payroll? No, he doesn't work here.
None of your business.
Well, thank heavens for that at least.
No killing needed.
- Don't be so sure.
- You'll see, honesty's best.
Yeah, well, honestly,
I'd like to kick your butt right now.
I'll take you.
But could you take me
to my couch first, please?
Thank you.
- Give me your arms. Get the tape off.
- Yeah.
All right, babe.
Very good at this. Thank you.
Thanks for your lovely tea.
- That was cruel. Why did you do that?
- Oh, it's this blindness nuisance.
It makes me mean. I'm sorry.
- But you two do need to talk.
- There's nothing to talk about.
Is this it?
- Uh...
- Sorry.
White CD with "RPB"
written on it in black?
Could be. You have a lot to talk about.
Like what?
Is it serious, you and coffee-cart man?
It's too early to tell.
I'd like to meet him.
What floor does he work on?
He doesn't. He's a lawyer.
- Ah.
- He was just visiting.
And no offense, but why does
my personal life have any concern to you?
Or Rigsby for that matter?
Well, me, I'm just nosy.
But Rigsby, he loves you.
He's just scared
of emotional commitment.
You're attracted to him,
but you're deeply repressed...
- ...and emotionally shut down.
- Is that right?
Because of a trauma in your past
that you've never spoken of, to anyone.
Ever. Even yourself.
Sorry. I was just thinking out loud.
What? I wasn't listening.
What's his name?
- Dan.
Can I meet him?
- If you like.
- I would.
Here's your client list.
I'll run it against
the Lynch-Halstead records.
One match.
You both shared a client a long time ago.
Carol Gentry?
Carol Gentry.
She forgives you, Carol.
Your mother truly forgives you.
I don't understand, Mr. Jane.
She forgives me?
Yes.
That's what she says.
And I believe it to be sincere.
She was a vicious, evil,
abusive woman.
But I loved her and cared for her
like a good daughter.
What did I ever do
that she should forgive me for?
It's a hard truth, Carol...
...but people don't change
when they pass on.
They simply become the essence
of who they are.
Your mother was a very complicated...
She forgives me?
That lunatic bitch forgives me?
People are very complicated.
Aren't they?
I'm afraid that's all we have time for
this week.
Okay, yeah.
I'm sorry. I just...
It's okay. Just breathe.
We'll talk more about this next time.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Thank you, Mr. Jane.
- Thank you.
Jane? You all right?
- Jane? You all right?
- Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Jane.
- Is he all right?
- Oh, I'm a hundred percent okay.
- No need to send me back.
- Sir, he needs to be in a hospital.
He has to go if you order him to.
I could, but someone did try
to kill him, remember?
We can protect him better here.
At less expense.
- Thanks, Virgil.
- Okay.
But this is a favor. If you die
in this department, I'm responsible.
I do all the paperwork.
If he does die for whatever reason,
move him to a public area, would you?
I'd be very grateful.
- I hope he's smiling.
- Places to be.
Don't we all?
A little help here?
Just the stick. Just the stick.
Thank you.
We started doing research
on your old client Carol Gentry.
- She's not a suspect.
- Lynch-Halstead were her brokerage firm.
- Just a coincidence. She's not a suspect.
- How can you be so sure?
Carol Gentry killed herself
eight years ago. She left no family.
You all still here?
We're all here.
Good. So back to square one, I guess.
Not quite. Van Pelt's done
some deeper research.
We cross-checked spouse's names
and came up with a second hit.
You used to have a client named
Jill Lamont. Her husband was Paul Krager.
He used to work for Lynch-Halstead.
Jill Lamont.
Yes.
Tell me more about your husband.
Just anything.
He loves me. Loves our son.
Family is everything to him.
But I've noticed a change lately.
What sort of a change?
He seems preoccupied.
And that's when you began to wonder
if he was being unfaithful?
- That's right.
- Right.
Something is coming through.
Feel it with me.
Here.
Yes, I'm feeling that Paul hasn't been
a hundred percent honest with you.
He hasn't been happy.
You know that, don't you?
Do you sense someone else in his life?
Your senses never lie.
- Yes. Yes, I do.
- Okay.
There is someone else. Is he leaving me?
You have to talk to him, Jill.
You have to tell Paul not to ruin
what you have together.
Paul Krager's a name
I haven't heard in a while.
Never even entered my mind.
What do you know
about his personal life?
We've all made our mistakes
over the years.
Fat wallets and good wine
can do that to a man.
You're referring to his divorce?
That was no divorce, that was a massacre.
His wife remarried, I think.
But Krager's whole world fell apart.
Work-wise, he never recovered.
Went off the rails. We had to let him go.
Who actually did the firing?
Now that you mention it,
Jimmy Medina did.
Jim did a lot of the ax work here.
Unfortunate part of the job.
- Any idea where we can find Krager?
- Last I heard, someone saw him...
...at a church soup kitchen
during the holidays.
There but for the grace of God,
if you know what I mean.
Lynch was right. The legal fees alone
nearly bankrupted Krager.
His wife took their son,
moved east, remarried.
- So where's Krager now?
- Based on what we found...
...he was so devastated losing his family,
his world collapsed.
No current address.
He hasn't filed a tax return in years.
His last known employer
was Lynch-Halstead in 2001.
- Boy, you really did a number on him.
- Yes, I did. Thank you.
No. You simply confirmed
what she knew in her heart already.
Has anyone tried contacting her?
Jill Lamont?
I left word. No answer yet.
We put an APB out on Paul Krager.
Cho and I will follow up on some leads.
You stay right there.
Nobody take him anywhere.
No excitement whatsoever. Clear?
- Clear, boss.
Crystal.
- Did you see how many clients Jane had?
- He helped a lot of people.
I'm not so sure.
Hi. Can I help you?
- Hey.
- Dan. Hey.
- Hi.
- Hi. What are you doing here?
I was at another meeting upstairs.
Thought I'd stop by and say hello.
Is that cool?
Yeah, totally.
No, it's just a surprise, that's all.
So introduce me to your colleague,
who keeps staring at me so strangely.
Yeah.
Agent Rigsby, this is my friend
Dan Hollenbeck.
- Good to meet you.
- How you doing?
- I'm excellent. And you?
- Good. Yeah.
- Okay, so...
- Lawyer, are you?
I am.
- I'm sorry. Do we have a problem?
- No. No problem. Takes all sorts.
- Even lawyers.
- Okay, that's enough.
A pleasure to get to know you,
Agent Rigsby.
Can we be somewhere private
for a moment?
- I don't know if that's such a good idea.
- Please?
You know, I'm sorry.
You and me do have a problem.
Not a big one, but we need to talk.
No trouble, I swear.
- All right, then.
- No, it is not all right.
- No trouble, I promise.
- It's okay, Grace. It's fine.
Okay.
So here we are. Talk away.
I don't know you, Dan.
Maybe you're a nice guy. I hope so.
I don't know. Because if you hurt Grace,
I will find you and cause you pain.
Because she means a lot to...
To the unit.
- So you treat her right, okay?
- Yeah, I hear you.
I appreciate your concern.
You care for Grace. Don't worry, I'm a...
I'm a nice guy.
Okay.
Hey, sorry to get heavy with you.
I had to say it, you know?
- So long as we understand each other.
- Yeah, sure thing. I understand. I do.
I am so embarrassed.
What did Rigsby say to you?
No call for embarrassment.
He's a good-hearted person. I like him.
He just wants you to be happy, or else.
- And what did you say?
- Well, I had to say I'd do my best.
- You did?
- I did.
Hey, where's this psychic character
you told me about?
- I'm dying to meet him.
- He wanted to meet you too.
Jane?
Damn.
Sorry, I didn't know
whether to wake you or not.
I'm awake.
You said you wanted to meet
the man I've been dating.
- Yeah. Is he coming?
- He's here.
Here?
- Here now?
- Yes.
- Right here.
- Oh.
Dan Hollenbeck, sir.
It's a real pleasure to meet you.
- Grace has told me so much about you.
- Good to meet you too, Dan.
- Excuse my asking, but are you...?
- Blind? Yes. As a bat.
- Temporarily blind. Think positive.
- Yes. Positive. That's right.
So, Van Pelt, where is Rigsby exactly?
I don't know.
Out getting pizza, if I know Rigsby.
- You need him for something?
- Lisbon? Cho?
Still chasing down Paul Krager.
- Nobody here but us.
- Of course.
So, Dan, quite the hard grip
you have there.
Working man's hands.
That faint scent of chemicals.
But an expensive Italian suit.
It's interesting.
Dan's a lawyer.
A very junior lawyer.
I lobby the state senate.
You're good with your hands,
good at building things. A hobby, maybe.
I guess.
What sort of things do you build
as a hobby?
You know, stuff.
And your parents? Where are they?
They're dead.
Sorry to be a busybody. Want to be sure
Grace finds the right young man.
Hush.
Well, I'm hungry. I guess I'll just
get myself something to eat.
- Don't be silly. I'll get you something.
- No, I can manage.
Think I'm dumb? Make the
wrong move and I'll shoot her in the head.
I hear you.
- What are you guys whispering about?
- Nothing.
- Some chips would be nice.
- What kind?
I'm easy.
It's the boss.
Looks like we've cracked it.
We found Paul Krager.
He was obsessed with Jane and Medina.
Remember he has a son?
Krager told us he's living in the city now.
He goes by the name Dan Hollenbeck.
Van Pelt?
- Sorry about this.
- Van Pelt?
That was weird.
I don't understand.
He's the bomber.
He killed Medina.
Now he's come to kill me.
Don't even think about it.
I'm sorry I had to lie to you, Grace.
Truly. But I needed you.
- Why?
- To access the statehouse lot.
- He used your security pass.
- You son of a bitch.
Just be cool, Van Pelt. Please be cool.
Grace, relax.
I have no desire to hurt you.
Give it up, Dan. Please.
I'm in too deep. I can't stop now.
Don't make me hurt you.
Just do as he says.
Oh, you're a nice guy now, aren't you?
You destroyed my life. For what?
Because my dad cheated on my mom?
Big deal. He wasn't perfect.
And for that, he's on the street.
He loses everything.
One day I'm at the best,
the best private school in Los Angeles.
I'm playing soccer
with movie stars' kids.
Next minute I'm in Dogpatch, New Jersey
with my weeping mom...
...getting my ass whipped by thugs
that don't even speak freaking English.
Why?
Because you,
you had to be the man who knows.
You had tell my mom the truth.
- I'm sorry, Dan.
- Yeah, sure you are.
With a gun at your back.
Take out your handcuffs.
Handcuff yourself.
Behind the back. Drop the cane.
Okay. Here we go.
- Let's go.
- Where are we going?
Somewhere quiet and private.
You won't like it.
Where's your car, Grace?
In the side parking lot.
A Jeep. Iowa plates.
I didn't know you were from Iowa.
Famous potatoes, huh?
That's Idaho, you ignorant jerk.
- Oh, yeah? What's Iowa famous for?
- Gullible women.
- That's not fair.
- Keep moving.
Tommy, you're still here.
Hey, Mr. Jane. Just locking up.
You folks need anything?
Uh...
Run. Run, Grace.
Freeze.
Okay, go to the right. The right.
- You're gonna take us to your car.
- But I can't drive.
- We'll manage. Keys, keys.
- My front pants pocket.
Sorry. Oh, oh.
- Got it. Got it. Let's go.
- Okay. Okay.
- The Jeep's on the right. On the right.
- That it?
Yeah. Okay.
Okay, there's the handle.
- You in, Grace? Grace, you in?
- Hang on. Hang on.
- On the dash or on the column?
- On the column.
Up. Up. Okay? Up.
- All right, that's reverse. Back it up.
- Good. All clear?
Yeah, slow. Slow.
Slowly. Slowly backing. Slowly.
Okay, slow, slow, slow.
Sorry about that.
- Straight.
- Okay, got it.
Okay. Straight, straight, straight.
Now, you're gonna make a right.
Turn right. No, not yet. Not yet.
Sorry about that.
Punch it, punch it, punch it.
Go right now. Oh, my God.
Okay. Reverse, reverse, reverse.
- You all right?
- Yeah, reverse, reverse. Go. Reverse.
Come on. Stop. Come on.
Come on, come on.
Okay, put it in park. Put it in park.
- Start. I can't start.
- Jane, go.
Oh, thank God. Oh, thank God.
What? What happened?
Did something good happen?
Didn't I say no excitement of any kind?
Oh, you're alive.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, it's no bother. I'm fine.
I'm sorry. God, I'm so sorry.
It's all right. It's all right.
Oops. Sorry about that.
I have an H746B form to fill out. Yeah.
Oh, you have no notion how good it is
to see your face, Rigsby.
Rigsby?
Ah!
You're funny.